Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 2012
  - Wirtz, James. J. and Peter R. Lavoy (eds.), Over the horizon proliferation threats., 2012 (Box 4)
  - Morson, Gary Saul, The long and short of it: from aphorism to novel., 2012 (Box 4)
  - Rozman, Gilbert (ed.), East Asian national identities: common roots and Chinese exceptionalism., 2012 (Box 4)
  - Bano, Masooda, Breakdown in Pakistan: how aid is eroding institutions for collective action., 2012 (Box 4)
  - Fisher, Cass, Contemplative nation: a philosophical account of Jewish theological language., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Marquardt, Michael J. and Roland K. Yeo, Breakthrough problem solving with action learning., 2012 (Box 5)
  - LaSalle, Mick, The beauty of the real: what Hollywood can learn from contemporary French actresses., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Rodriguez O., Jamie E., "We are now the true Spaniards:" sovreignity, revolution, independence, and the emergence of the Federal Republic of Mexico, 1808-1824., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Marshall, Jonathan V., The Lebanese connection: corruption, civil war, and the international drug traffic., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Griffin, Abbie, Raymond L. Price, and Bruce A. Vojak, Serial innovators: how individuals create and deliver breakthrough innovations in mature firms., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Arum, Richard and Melissa Velez (eds.), Improving learning environments: school discipline and student achievement in comparative perspective., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Fethke, Gary C. and Andrew J. Policano, Public no more: a new path to excellence for America's public universities., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Bilenky, Serhiy, Romantic nationalism in eastern Europe: Russian, Polish, and Ukrainian political imagnations., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Bliss, Catherine, Race decoded: the genomic fight for social justice., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Dhingra, Pawan, Life behind the lobby: Indian American motel owners and the American dream., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Roth, Wendy D., Race migrations: Latinos and the cultural transformation of race., 2012 (Box 5)
  - Love, Joseph, The revolt of the whip., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Bornstein, Erica, Disquieting gifts: humanitarianism in New Delhi., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Binder, Guyora, Felony murder., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Sebbah, Francois-David, Testing the limit: Derrida, Henry, Levinas, and the phenomenological tradition., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Sabet, Daniel M., Police reform in Mexico: informal politics and the challenge of institutional change., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Pansters, Wil G., Violence, coercion, and state-making in twentieth-century Mexico., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Gordon, Robert S.C., The Holocaust in Italian culture, 1944-2010., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Hess, Edward D. and Jeanne Liedtka, The physics of business growth: mindsets, system, and processes., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Szalay, Michael, Hip figures: a literary history of the Democratic Party., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lianos, Ioannis and D. Daniel Sokol(eds)., The global limits of competition law., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Coleman, Susan and Alicia M. Robb, A Rising Tide: Financing Strategies for Women-Owned Firms., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Pisters, Patricia, The neuro-image: a Deleuzian film-philosophy of digital screen culture., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Sarfaty, Galit A., Values in translation: human rights and the culture of the World Bank., 2012 (Box 6)
  - Waddock, Sandra and Andreas Rasche, Building the responsible enterprise: where vision and values add value., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Esmier, Samera, Juridical humanity: a colonial history., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Woeste, Victoria Saker, Henry Ford's War on Jews and the Battle against Hate Speech., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Suominen, Kati, Peerless and periled: the paradox of American leadership in the world economic order., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Rensmann, Lars and Samir Gandesha, Arendt and Adorno: political and philosophical investigations., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Lawler, Edward E., III, and John W. Boudreau, Effective human resource management: a global analysis., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Arnson, Cynthia J. (ed), In the Wake of War: Democratization and Internal Armed Conflict in Latin America., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Teichman, Judith A., Social forces and states: poverty and distributional outcomes in South Korea, Chile, and Mexico., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Innerarity, Daniel, The future and its enemies: in defense of political hope., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Kinsey, Christopher and Malcolm Hugh Patterson (eds), Contractors and war: the transformation of US expeditionary operations., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Shever, Elana, Resources for reform: oil and neoliberalism in Argentina., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Ury, Scott, Barricades and banners: the revolution of 1905 and the transformation of Warsaw Jewry., 2012 (Box 7)
  - Goldman, Andrea S., Opera and the city: the politics of culture in Beijing, 1770-1900., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Aydin, Aysegul, Foreign powers and intervention in armed conflicts., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Bender, John, Ends of enlightenment., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Furani, Khaled, Silencing the sea: secular rhythms in Palestinean poetry., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Reynolds, Nancy C., A city consumed: urban commerce, the Cairo fire, and the politics of decolonization in Egypt., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Kimmage, Michael, In history's grip: Philip Roth's Newark trilogy., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Banzhaf, H. Spencer, The political economy of environmental justice., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Ricciardi, Alessia, After la dolce vita: a cultural prehistory of Berlusconi's Italy., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Tarr, G. Alan, Without fear or favor: judicial independence and judicial accountability in the states., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Devin, Lee and Robert D. Austin, The soul of design: harnessing the power of plot to create extraordinary products., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Bashkin, Orit, New Babylonians: a history of Jews in modern Iraq., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Hughey, Matthew T., White bound: nationalists, antiracists, and the shared meanings of race., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Preston, Lee E. and James E. Post, Private management and public policy: the principle of public responsibility., 2012 (Box 8)
  - Mieszkowski, Jan, Watching war., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Mahnken, Thomas G., Competitive strategies for the 21st century: theory, history, and practice., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Nealon, Jeffrey T., Post-postmodernism: or, the cultural logic of just-in-time capitalism., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Fukuoka, Maki, The premise of fidelity: science, visuality, and representing the real in nineteenth-century Japan., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Pierce, Jennifer L., Racing for innocence: whiteness, gender, and the backlash against affirmative action., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Agius Vallejo, Jody, Barrios to burbs: the making of the Mexican-American middle class., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Svallfors, Stefan (ed.), Contested welfare states: welfare attitudes in Europe and beyond., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Knopf, Jeffrey W. (ed.), Security assurances and nuclear nonproliferation., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Crowe, Ian, Patriotism and public spirit: Edmund Burke and the role of the critic in mid-18th-century Britain., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Suarez-Potts, William J., The making of law: the Supreme Court and labor legislation in Mexico, 1875-1931., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Goldstein, Avery and Edward D. Mansfield, eds., The nexus of economics, security, and international relations in Asia., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Birnbaum, Pierre, A tale of ritual murder in the age of Louis XIV: the trial of Rafael Levy, 1669., 2012 (Box 9)
  - Murphy-Shigematsu, Stephen, When half is whole: multiethnic Asian American identities., 2012 (Box 10)
  - Gumbrecht, Hans Ulrich, Atmosphere, mood, Stimmung: on a hidden potential of literature., 2012 (Box 10)
  - Grodsky, Brian, Social movements and the new state: the fate of pro-democracy organizations when democracy is won., 2012 (Box 10)
  - Falk, Candace (ed.), Emma Goldman: a documentary history of the American years, volume 3: light and shadows, 1910-1916., 2012 (Box 10)
  - Matt, Daniel C. (translator and commentator), The Zohar, Pritzker edition, volume 7., 2012 (Box 10)
  - Atlan, Henri, The sparks of randomness volume 2: the atheism of scripture., 2012 (Box 10)
  - Hall, Linda B., Dolores del Rio: beauty in light and shade., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Cuellar, Mariano-Florentino, Governing security: the hidden origins of American security agencies., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Shapiro, Ruth A. (ed.), The real problem solvers: social entrepreneurs in America., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Shohet, Azriel, The Jews of Pinsk, 1881 to 1941., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Torre Curiel, Jose Refugio de la, Twilight of the mission frontier: shifting interethnic alliances and social organization in Sonora, 1768-1855., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Miller, Elizabeth Carolyn, Slow print: literary radicalism and late Victorian print culture., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Lopez-Alonso, Moramay, Measuring up: a history of living standards in Mexico, 1850-1950., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Stern, Sheldon M., The Cuban Missile Crisis in American memory: myths versus reality., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Kyriakides, Christopher and Rodolfo D. Torres, Race defaced: paradigms of pessimism, politics of possibility., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Wenger, Andreas and Alex Wilner, Deterring terrorism: theory and practice., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Luhmann, Niklas, Theory of society, volume 1., 2012 (Box 11)
  - Bishara, Amahl A., Back stories: U.S. news production and Palestinian politics., 2012 (Box 11)
- 2013
  - Campe, Rudiger, Literature and calculation from Pascal to Kleist., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Faulk, Karen Ann, In the wake of neoliberalism: citizenship and human rights in Argentina., 2013 (Box 1)
  - McCumber, John, On philosophy: notes from a crisis., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Braverman, Irus, Zooland: the instituion of captivity., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Pizzigoni, Caterina, The life within: local indigenous society in Mexico's Toluca Valley, 1650-1800., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Azoulay, Ariella and Adi Ophir, The one-state condition: occupation and democracy in Israel/Palestine., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Rodriguez-Campos, Liliana and Rigoberto Rincones-Gomez, Collaborative evaluations step-by-step., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Fry, Louis W. and Melissa Sadler Nisiewicz, Maximizing the triple bottom line through spiritual leadership., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Khan, Feroz Hassan, Eating grass: the making of the Pakistani bomb., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Fetterman, David M., Empowerment evaluation in the digital villages: Hewlett-Packard's $15 million race toward social justice., 2013 (Box 1)
  - Heydemann, Steven and Reinoud Leenders (eds.), Middle east authoritarianisms: governance, contestation, and regime resilience in Syria and Iran., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Powell, Eve M. Troutt, Tell this in my memory: stories of enslavement from Egypt, Sudan, and the Ottoman Empire., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Martinez, Ernesto Javier, On making sense: queer race narratives of intelligibility., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Khalili, Laleh, Time in the shadows; confinement in counterinsurgencies., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Leighton, Wayne A. and Edward J. Lopez, Madmen, intellectuals, and academic scribblers: the economic engine of political change., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Cook-Martin, David, The scramble for citizens: dual nationality and state competition for immigrants., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Surak, Kristin, Making tea, making Japan: cultural nationalism in practice., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Luhmann, Niklas, A systems theory of religion., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Guest, Stephen, Ronald Dworkin (3rd edition)., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Becker, Jo, Campaigning for justice: human rights advocacy in practice., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Ascher, Abraham, Was Hitler a riddle? Western democracies and national socialism., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich, Human, all too human II and unpublished fragments from the period of Human, all too human II (spring 1878-fall 1879)., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Drori, Israel, Shmuel Ellis, and Zur Shapira, The evolution of a new industry: a genealogical approach., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Biemann, Asher D., Dreaming of Michelangelo: Jewish variations on a modern theme., 2013 (Box 2)
  - Wolff, Larry, Paolina's innocence: child abuse in Casanova's Venice., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Sanos, Sandrine, The aesthetics of hate: far-right intellectuals, antisemitism, and gender in 1930s France., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Gasche, Rodolphe, Georges Bataille: phenomenology and phantasmatology., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Kaldor, Mary, New and old wars: organized violence in a global era (3rd edition)., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Kelle, Alexander, Kathryn Nixdorff, and Malcolm Dando, Preventing a biochemical arms race., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Janack, Marianne, What we mean by experience., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Sarat, Austin, Lawrence Douglas, and Martha Merrill Umphrey, The secrets of law., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Marion, Jean-Luc, In the self's place: the approach of Saint Augustine., 2013 (Box 3)
  - Seawright, Jason, Party-system collapse: the roots of crisis in Peru and Venezuela., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Shapiro, Barbara J., Political communication and political culture in England, 1558-1688., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Oakes, Amy, Diversionary war: domestic unrest and international conflict., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Elyada, Amy, A goy who speaks Yiddish: Christians and the Jewish language in early modern Germany., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Cohn, Willy, No justice in Germany: the Breslau diaries, 1933-1941., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Esposito, Roberto, Living thought: the origins and actuality of Italian philosophy., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Cross, Frank B., The failed promise of originalism., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Gilbert, Nora, Better left unsaid: Victorian novels, Hays Code films, and the benefits of censorship., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Anagost, Ann, Andrea Arai, and Hai Ren, Global futures in East Asia: youth, nation, and the new economy in uncertain times., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Olson, Jess, Nathan Birnbaum and Jewish modernity: architect of Zionism, Yiddishism, and orthodoxy., 2013 (Box 4)
  - Weigel, Sigrid, Walter Benjamin images, the creaturely, and the holy., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Beard, T. Randolph, David L. Kaserman, and Rigmar Osterkamp, The global organ shortage: economic causes, human consequences, policy responses., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Rogers, Rebecca, A Frenchwoman's imperial story: Madame Luce in nineteenth-century Algeria., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Aspinwall, Mark, Side effects: Mexican governance under NAFTA's labor and environmental agreements., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Ossman, Susan, Moving matters: paths of serial migration., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Clune, Michael, Writing against time., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Funk, Jeffrey L., Technology change and the rise of new industries., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Zurcher, Christoph et. al., Costly democracies: peacebuilding and democratization after war., 2013 (Box 5)
  - Jackson, Michelle (ed.), Determined to succeed? Performance versus choice in educational attainment., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Stulberg, Adam N. and Matthew Fuhrman (eds)., The nuclear renaissance and international security., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Komisaruk, Catherine, Labor and love in Guatemala., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Boletsi, Maria, Barbarism and its discontents., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Mosca, Matthew W., From frontier policy to foreign policy: the question of India and the transformation of geopolitics in Qing China., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Jeffries, Michael P., Paint the White House black: Barack Obama and the meaning of race in America., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Forman, Janis, Story telling in business: the authentic and fluent organization., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Grebowicz, Margret, Why Internet porn matters., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Namikas, Lise, Battleground Africa: cold war in the Congo, 1960-1965., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Dowling, Julie A. and Jonathan Xavier Inda (eds.), Governing immigration through crime: a reader., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Meyer-Fong, Tobie, What remains: coming to terms with civil war in 19th century China., 2013 (Box 6)
  - Grayson, David and Jane Nelson, Corporate responsibility coalitions: the past, present, and future of alliances for sustainable capitalism., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Foster, Elizabeth A., Faith in empire: religion, politics, and colonial rule in French Senegal, 1860-1940., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Walker, Louise E., Waking from the dream: Mexico's middle classes after 1968., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Anderson, Patrick L., The economics of business valuation: towards a value functional analysis., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Guenoun, Denis, About Europe: philosophical hypotheses., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Etkind, Alexander, Warped mourning: stories of the undead in the land of the unburied., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Staheli, Urs, Spectacular speculation: thrills,the economy, and popular discourse., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Gaiduk, Ilya V., Divided together: the United States and the Soviet Union in the United Nations, 1945-1965., 2013 (Box 7)
  - Polillo, Simone, Conservatives versus wildcats: a sociology of financial conflict., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Eoyang, Glenda H. and Royce J. Holladay, Adaptive action: leveraging uncertainty in your organization., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Van Hollen, Cecilia, Birth in the age of AIDS: women, reproduction, and HIV/AIDS in India., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Freedman, Alisa, Laura Miller, and Christine R. Yano (eds)., Modern girls on the go: gender, mobility, and labor in Japan., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Scott, Craig R., Anonymous agencies, backstreet businesses, and covert collectives: rethinking organizations in the 21st century., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Jennings, Theodore W., Outlaw justice: the Messianic politics of Paul., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Kim, Jaesok, Chinese labor in a Korean factory: class, ethnicity, and productivity on the shop floor in globalizing China., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Osburg, John, Anxious wealth: money and morality among China's new rich., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Coyne, Chritopher J., Doing bad by doing good: why humanitarian action fails., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Mandell, Robert, Global security upheaval: armed nonstate groups usurping state stability functions., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Simmons, Solon, The eclipse of equality: arguing America on Meet the press., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Haugerud, Angelique, No billionaire left behind: satirical activism in America., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Bayat, Asef, Life as politics: how ordinary people change the Middle East., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Agamben, Giorgio, The highest poverty: monastic rules and form-of-life., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Ehrenfield, John R. and Andrew J. Hoffman, Flourishing: a frank conversation about sustainability., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Davidson, Stephen M., A new era in U.S. health care: critical next steps under the Affordable Care Act., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Hough, Douglas E., Irrationality in health care: what behavioral economics reveals about what we do and why., 2013 (Box 8)
  - Hess, Jonathan M., Maurice Samuels, and Nadia Valman (eds)., Nineteenth-century Jewish literature., 2013 (Box 9)
  - Chavez, Leo R., The Latino threat: constructing immigrants, citizens, and the nation (second edition)., 2013 (Box 9)
  - Allen, Lori, The rise and fall of human rights: cynicism and politics in occupied Palestine., 2013 (Box 9)
  - 2013 (Box 9)
  - Gumbrecht, Hans Ulrich, After 1945: latency as origin of the present., 2013 (Box 9)
  - Christensen, Mark Z., Nahua and Maya Catholicisms: texts and religion in colonial central Mexico and Yucatan., 2013 (Box 9)
  - Glass, Loren, Counter-culture colophon: Grove Press, the Evergreen Review, and the incorporation of the avant-garde., 2013 (Box 9)
  - Lane, L. W. "Bill," Jr., The sun never sets: reflections on a western life., 2013 (Box 9)
  - Frieden, Menachem Mendel, A Jewish life on three continents: the memoir of Menachem Mendel Frieden., 2013 (Box 10)
  - Iqbal, Muhammad, The reconstruction of religious thought in Islam., 2013 (Box 10)
  - Corley, Pamela C., Amy Steigerwalt, and Artemus Ward, The puzzle of unanimity: consensus on the United States Supreme Court., 2013 (Box 10)
  - Angelina Godoy, Of Medicines and Markets: Intellectual Property and Human Rights in the Free Trade Era., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Ferber, Ilit, Philosophy and Melancholy: Benjamin's Early Reflections on Theater and Language., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Group, Radmila. After Yugoslavia: The Cultural Spaces of a Vanished Land (Stanford Studies on Central and Eastern)., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Donati, Sabina, A Political History of National Citizenship and Identity in Italy, 1861–1950., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Lefebvre, Alexandre, Human Rights as a Way of Life: On Bergson's Political Philosophy (Cultural Memory in the Present)., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Tom Snijders and Victor Nee, T he Handbook of Rational Choice Social Research., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Benjamin, Ruha, People's Science: Bodies and Rights on the Stem Cell Frontier., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Moore, Aaron, Constructing East Asia: Technology, Ideology, and Empire in Japan’s Wartime Era, 1931-1945., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Kraay, Hendrik, Days of National Festivity in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1823-1889., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Redish, Martin, The Adversary First Amendment: Free Expression and the Foundations of American Democracy., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Kim, Sun Joo, Voice from the North: Resurrecting Regional Identity Through the Life and Work of Yi Sihang (1672–1736)., 2013 (Box 11)
  - Goodale, Mark, and Nancy Postero, Neoliberalism, Interrupted: Social Change and Contested Governance in Contemporary Latin America., 2013 (Box 11)